

# **VICTOR P. NG**

www.vpng.design linkedin.com/in/victorpng vpangng@gmail.com 781.697.7745

I'm a designer who applies design skills in innovative, interesting, and creative ways. I am motivated by multidisciplinary teamwork and continuous self-improvement. My goal is to work alongside creative minds to enhance user experiences and build products that are sustainable and intuitive.

# **SKILLS**

UX Design
Interaction Design
Visual Design
User Research
Usability Testing
Graphic Design
Wireframing & Prototyping
Cross-Functional Teamwork

## **TOOLS**

Adobe XD Sketch Figma Illustrator Photoshop

InVision

**GitHub** 

HTML / CSS / JavaScript

#### **PROJECTS**

# UX Designer | General Assembly Hackathon

Aug 2019

- Collaborated with developers to create homeless resource app.
- Produced project deliverables under 2 days.
- Designed paper prototypes, sketches, and wireframes.

## Interaction Designer | Hazel Analytics

Jul 2019

- Designed wireframes and interactive prototype for user testing.
- Delivered 4 product features of food safety app under 3 weeks.
- Conducted and facilitated design studio session with client stakeholders.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Visual UX Design Intern | Mentorz

Sep 2019 - Current

- Collected qualitative data through user interviews and surveys. Synthesized findings through affinity mapping.
- Design wireframes and mockups based on user flows. Conducted onsite usability testing and redesigned UI for the mobile application.
- Collaborated with developers to streamline app and web experience.

## **Graphic Designer** | The World is Fun

Nov 2018 - Current

- Produced and updated physical materials for the organization with over 5,000 volunteers and 90 staff members.
- Worked collaboratively with design team to create client needs such as signage, posters, anniversary logos, and volunteer badges.
- Created visual assets for the website and marketing pieces for the organization as needed.

# **End User Computing Analyst** | Shire Pharmaceuticals

May 2016 - Mar 2017

- Managed day to day operations in multiple buildings of the Shire Lexington, MA campus, comprising of approximately 1000+ end users.
- Responded to user service calls and service tickets to troubleshoot and resolve reported incidents at the tier 1 level.
- Handled customer communications and initiatives to realize improved customer service and satisfaction.

#### **EDUCATION**

General Assembly 2019 | User Experience Design Immersive

Seattle University 2017 - 2018 | Web Development Certificate

University of Massachusetts Amherst 2011 - 2014 | BA Information Design